<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Xinyi Wang</title>
    <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Xinyi Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Server Migration to AWS (Internship at Amazon)</title>
      <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/amazonintern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/amazonintern/</guid>
      <description>Trasanction Stroage &amp;amp; Config Team&#xA;Introdunction What I did Motivation Result High-level Design Details Why Stepfunction rather than EC2? Why do I plan to use AWS CDK instead of CloudFormation? How do I make sure the code quality? Introdunction Achieve the workflow(BatchMoveEndpoint) in AWS and demonstrate the server(SableManagementServer) can be implemented in Native AWS.&#xA;PDF: [Proof of Conceop] SableManagementServer BatchMoveEndpoints in NAWS: Design Doc&#xA;What I did Migrated the BatchMoveEndpoint (BME) workflow to AWS, ensuring full implementation of SableManagementServer (SMS) within the native AWS environment, which reduced 128 maintenance tickets annually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat and Dog Recognition Based on CNN Convolutional Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/catdogrecognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/catdogrecognition/</guid>
      <description>Here is PDF: Cat and Dog Recognition Based on CNN Convolutional Neural Network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PapyrusAI - An tool for use in higher education courses</title>
      <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/papyrusai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/papyrusai/</guid>
      <description>About PapyrusAI was developed by the Digital Learning Lab at the University of California, Irvine, in partnership with the Samueli School of Engineering, as part of an NSF grant (#23152984).&#xA;While our initial goal is to develop this tool for use in higher education courses, we received a Proof of Product grant from UCI’s Beall Applied Innovation Center to adapt the tool for secondary school and determine the marketability and feasibility of commercializing PapyrusAI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart home communication network and control system - Internship at CAS</title>
      <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/smarthome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/smarthome/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StayBooking - An online stay rental application</title>
      <link>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/staybooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangxinyiu.github.io/projects/staybooking/</guid>
      <description>What I did Deomo: https://recordit.co/cXdWcj0ahV&#xA;Designed and built a single-page web application using React. Bootstrap the development with mature component library Ant Design. Implemented the backend services based on Spring Boot to support stay upload, delete, search, and reserve functionality. Used MySQL to store user-generated data, e.g. stay information and reservation history, and utilized Google Cloud Storage to store media files for uploaded stays. Created geo index by Elasticsearch to support geo-based stay search based on user’s selected locations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
